A Family's Desperate Search For Their Missing Daughter
Race Against Time: The Search for Sarah is a drama,
thriller, crime film directed by Fred Gerber.
The true story of the disappearance of Sarah Porter.
With no help from the police, Sarah's parents are
forced to act on their own to find her.
They must battle the bureaucracy of the police department while they are
searching all over town for clues to Sarah's whereabouts.
When the crucial clue is discovered, Sarah's father
confronts her kidnapper at gunpoint.
Danielle, played by Katy Boyer.
Lydia, played by Missy Crider.
John Porter, played by Richard Crenna.
Natalie Porter, played by Patty Duke.
Sarah Porter, played by Ele Keats.
Steve, played by Jon Gries.
Sarah Michelle Prinze (née Gellar  GHEL-ər; born
April 14, 1977) is an American actress.
She is known for portraying strong female characters in film and television, and
is regarded as a scream queen for her work in the horror genre.
After being spotted by a talent agent as a child, Gellar
began her career on television at age five.
She obtained her first leading role in the syndicated teen drama series Swans Crossing (1992) and had her breakthrough as
Kendall Hart on the ABC soap opera All My Children (1993–1995), for which she won a Daytime Emmy Award.
She achieved international recognition for her portrayal of Buffy Summers on the WB/UPN supernatural series Buffy
the Vampire Slayer (1997–2003), which earned her a Saturn Award and a nomination for a Golden Globe.
In film, Gellar has played leading and supporting roles in I Know What You Did Last Summer (1997), Scream 2 (1997), Cruel Intentions (1999), Scooby-Doo
(2002), Scooby-Doo 2: Monsters Unleashed (2004), The Grudge (2004), Southland Tales (2006), The Air I Breathe (2007),  and Do Revenge (2022).
Her other television credits include Ringer (2011–2012), The Crazy Ones
(2013–2014), Wolf Pack (2023), and Dexter: Original Sin (2024–2025).
As a voice actor, Gellar has appeared in the films Happily N'Ever After (2007) and TMNT (2007), the series Robot Chicken (2005–2018), Star
Wars Rebels (2015–2016), and Masters of the Universe: Revelation (2021), and the video game Call of Duty: Black Ops (2011).
In 2015, she co-founded Foodstirs, an e-commerce baking company.
Her cookbook, Stirring Up Fun with Food, was published in 2017.
The tone is emotional and intense.